Mss.Rec.122 Mss.Rec.122
American Philosophical Society
Nisgha material
1984
Mss.Rec.122
American Philosophical Society
5.0 Tape(s)
Grammatical elicitation of Nisgha sentences with consultants Sarah Picard and Will Stevenson, recorded by Wendy Thompson and Robert Belvin from June to August 1984. Location of recording not identified.
5 audiocassettes (2 hr., 3 min.): analog, 1 7/8 ips, stereo.
Belvin, Robert S.
Picard, Sarah
Thompson, Wendy H.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Wendy Thompson in 1985 (Acc. 1985 42r). This material was recorded with the assistance of a Phillips Fund grant.
Related Archival Material
Manuscript material accompanying this recording is available in the Phillips Fund Collection (Mss.497.3.Am4).
Indians of North America--British Columbia--Languages; Niska language; Sound recordings
- Audio recordings
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 06-06-1984, 1984-06-06; 01-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:42; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
    Existence and Location of Originals note
    This file is a compressed, digitized version of the original. The APS Library maintains the original format (Audiocassette) as well as an uncompressed digitized version of this recording.
    Niska language
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 06-11-1984, 1984-06-11; 01-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:51; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 06-13-1984, 1984-06-13; 01-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:05:52; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 06-15-1984, 1984-06-15; 01-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:04:44; Stevenson, Will; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 06-18-1984 [1 of 2], 1984-06-18; 01-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:47; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 06-18-1984 [2 of 2], 1984-06-18; 02-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:05:16; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 06-21-1984, 1984-06-21; 02-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:06:04; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 06-25-1984, 1984-06-25; 02-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:05:23; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 06-27-1984, 1984-06-27; 02-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:05:54; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 06-29-1984, 1984-06-29; 02-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:32; Stevenson, Will; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 07-31-1984 [1 of 2], 1984-07-31; 02-06; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:57; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 07-31-1984 [2 of 2], 1984-07-31; 03-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:47; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 08-01-1984, 1984-08-01; 03-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:06:45; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 08-02-1984, 1984-08-02; 03-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:02; Belvin, Robert S.; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 08-03-1984, 1984-08-03; 03-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:10:45; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 08-07-1984 [1 of 2], 1984-08-07; 03-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:47; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 08-07-1984 [2 of 2], 1984-08-07; 04-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:48; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 08-13-1984, 1984-08-13; 04-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:06; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 08-16-1984, 1984-08-16; 04-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:09:11; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 08-17-1984, 1984-08-17; 04-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:04:11; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 08-22-1984 [1 of 2], 1984-08-22; 04-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:00:58; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 08-22-1984 [2 of 2], 1984-08-22; 05-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:17; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.
  - Elicitation of Nisgha sentences, 08-24-1984, 1984-08-22; 05-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:55; Belvin, Robert S.; Picard, Sarah; Thompson, Wendy S.